Karltun Moreno

" I am a Full Stack Web Developer that lives and breathes digital media practices in order to find solutions for mobile first web development applications. This allows me to conduct a professional business that champions the expansion of new and existing brands." Specializing in React.js, Javascript, Express and Mysql.

https://github.com/karltunmoreno/My-Portfolio https://github.com/karltunmoreno

EXPERIENCE

Vauhlt - Miami. FL. Front End Developer August 2022 - April 2023

Created agile UI-UX web development in Next.js/React. This is a personal wallet for individual blockchain trading, purchasing and storing crypto assets and alike. Beta testing front-end to back-end accounting. Apex Chart, Node Sass, React Bootstrap, React-Perfect-Scrollbar, Typescript, CSS HTML, Github. https://karltunmoreno.github.io/Vauhlt/

Karltun Moreno 360 - Los Angeles, CA.

Full Stack Web Developer December 2020 - July 2022

Developed a full stack website with service pages, bookings, appointments, contact email form, fully mobile responsive app. Website for real estate content services. Used Matterport 3D, drones, video, Javascript, JQuery, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Photoshop, Final Cut Pro, Adobe Premiere & machine learning GPT. www.karltunmoreno360.com

Manuel Rodando - Miami, FL.

Full Stack Web Developer May 2020 - November 2020

Built a SPA, UI-UX for You Tube personality on social media platform with blog travel and talk show site. Linked DNS endpoints, setup domain Go Daddy, Used Adobe Dreamweaver, Photoshop, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, VS Code, GitHub. www.manuelrodando.com

Outer Bounds Pictures - Los Angeles, CA.

Full Stack Web Developer - CEO

March 2016 - May 2020

Designed a full stack website with service pages, bookings, appointments, contact email form, fully mobile responsive site with e-commerce art store. Visa, Master Card and Square payments setup. Photography, video services, apparel site. Used Javascript, JQuery, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Photoshop, Final Cut Pro, Adobe Premiere & machine learning GPT. www.outerboundspictures.com

EDUCATION

University of Miami, Coral Gables, FL.

Technical Certificate: Full Stack Web Development in Coding Javascript & Full Stack Development in MERN Stack. California State University (CSUN), Northridge, CA.

Bachelor in Psychology Studied Behavioral Science.

CONTACT

6911 Remmet Ave #208 Canoga Park, CA. 91303 (818)317-4178 Karltunmoreno@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/ karltunmoreno-0a910a46/

SKILLS

DRONE - UAS PART 107 CERTIFIED PHOTOGRAPHY - MATTERPORT 3D EDITING - VISUAL MEDIA GRAPHIC DESIGN BUDGETING & SCHEDULING GOOGLE SEARCH CENTRAL

FRONT END LANGUAGES

REACT.JS - NEXT. JS - IONIC - REDUX ADOBE DREAMWEAVER HTML - CSS **GIT HUB** JAVASCRIPT - TYPESCRIPT **BOOTSTRAP JQUERY - AJAX - JSON**

BACK END

NODE.JS EXPRESS.JS, MVC SQL / MYSQL/ ORM **HEROKU / JAWSDB** INSOMNIA / REST- API's (CRUD) MONGO DB / MONGOOSE / ATLAS / ODM APOLLO / GRAPHQL - API

SOFTWARE

POWER POINT / WORD / EXCEL ADOBE **PHOTOSHOP** ADOBE LIGHTROOM ADOBE ILLUSTRATOR & XD, FIGMA ADOBE PREMIERE PRO ADOBE AFTER EFFECTS ADOBE ACROBAT

MORE WEB PROJECTS

Food Fest - PWA- Html, CSS, Javascript, Bootstrap, Chrome Dev tools, Github. Application for quick offline uploading. Mobile UI responsive with home screen. Front-end stack. https:// karltunmoreno.github.io/Food-Fest/ Animal List Administrator - Rest Api, CRUD funtions, Javascript, Html, CSS, Node.js, Express.js. https:afternooncaverns-57263.herokuapp.com/ Just Geeky News - MVC - Javascript, Node.js, MySql, Express.js. https://protectedlowlands-09239.herokuapp.com/ Momentuum - React.js,

https://karltunmoreno.github.ia/nomentuum/ Task Manager - Html, CSS Javascript, Bootstrap, JQuery. https://karltunmoreno.github.io/Task-Manager/

Javascript, Html, CSS, Node.js.